原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译:  glida    Eunice油腻希
翻译:  洗七里   好看皮囊有趣赛
校对:  无趣丑妹再见赛
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十七集
最新海外影视剧下载
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
没干什么
Nothing!
不好意思  习惯了
Sorry. Habit.
我还真没做什么不该做的
I'm not actually doing anything wrong.
只是在看亚利桑那州立大学有没有录取我
Just checking to see if I got into A.S.U.
怎么不叫我们一起
Without us?!
大伙  快过来
Guys, get in here!
就是现在
It's happening!
菲尔在网上看了个视频
Phil saw videos online
全家人一起庆祝孩子被大学录取的一刻
of families celebrating the moment their kid got into college.
纯粹的戏剧性  当全家人紧张的期待
For pure drama, you can't beat that thing
变成无比的喜悦爆发出来
when an entire family's nervous anticipation
简直无与伦比
turns into an explosion of utter joy.
-来吧  -来吧  纽约大学
- Come on! - Come on, N-Y...
圣母大学
Notre...
靠
...Damn.
好了  开始吧
All righty, here we go.
开始录像
And record and...
"欢迎进入亚利桑那州"
"Welcome to Arizona State"...
-真的录取了  -我的天啊
- It's happening! - ‭Oh, my God!
"欢迎进入亚利桑那州立大学招生门户
"Welcome to Arizona State's admissions portal.
我们很遗憾地通知您"
"We regret to inform you"...
伙计
Aww, pal...
别搞悬念了
Well, don't leave us in suspense.
到底被录取没有
What did they say?
我刚刚看了一眼莉莉
Hey, I just peeked in on Lily,
你猜是谁蜷在她床上陪她睡觉
and guess who she was curled up with on her bed?
如果不是咱家的猫  我会因为你拿
If it's not the cat, I'm gonna be really upset about
这件事开玩笑而感到十分担忧
how you're teasing this out.
她能有只亲近的宠物我很开心
I love that she has a pet that she's close to
就像当初我和我的宠物猪莉莉一样
like I was with my pet pig Lily.
骗我给咱女儿取了培根的名字
Still no guilt, I see, after tricking me into
看来你至今仍不觉得内疚
naming our daughter after bacon.
我和那只宠物猪很亲近的
I was very close to that pig.
无论如何
For heaven's sakes,
我至今还把她的骨灰放在车库里
I still have her ashes in the garage.
是啊
True.
我最近开始在车库里健身
I recently started exercising in the garage,
在第一天  我
and on the first day, I, uh --
我就"掉"了好几斤
I dropped a couple of pounds.
我早知道米奇尔在骗我
I knew Mitchell was lying.
我只是给他个机会向我坦白
I was just giving him the opportunity to come clean.
我早就发现骨灰瓮空了
I had discovered the urn was empty.
莉莉
Lily?
你知道吗  我在想
You know, I was thinking tonight
今晚从你爸那回来后
maybe we could bury the ashes in the back yard
或许我们能把骨灰在后院下葬
after we get back from your dad's.
今晚悼念她再合适不过了
It's a perfect night to pay tribute.
-为什么  -今晚是猪月
- W-Why? ‭- The Pig Moon.
不好意思  再说一次
I'm sorry? One more time.
猪月
The Pig Moon.
每隔十八年  月亮会发出肉粉色的光晕
Every 18 years, the moon takes on a pink hue,
并与猎户座连成一线
and it aligns with Orion.
在我们老家是件大事
Oh. ‭It's a huge deal back home.
我们会办庆祝活动
There's a festival,
所有监狱都会大赦  以示善意
they empty out all the jails as a sign of goodwill.
所以我们今晚要办个仪式之类的吗
So, we're having, like, a ceremony tonight?
是的  宝贝
Yes, sweetie.
但我们不是要去爷爷家吗
But don't we have grandpa's?
没关系的
Well, you know what?
反正我们总是在找可信的借口好早点离开
We're always looking for a credible reason to leave early.
那到时我们该怎么说
So, what are we supposed to say?
"我们不吃甜点了  得早点回家
"No -- no dessert for us. We got to get home.
我们得把一头德国名种老母猪
We got to bury the 25-year-old ashes
25年的陈年骨灰埋了"
of a Brunswick King sow."
态度真不错
Wow. Nice attitude.
就像你故意想让猪月约翰老人
It's almost like you want Pig Moon John
在你的狩猎靴里装满煤块似的
to fill your hunting boot with coal.
这也太慢了
This is so slow!
如果你在浏览普里契特衣柜的网页
If you're on the Pritchett's Closets website,
我们已经知道加载速度慢的事了
we're aware of the slowdown.
要么是被黑客黑了
It's either a hack by the Chinese
要么是我雇来改善网页的坑货[黑客]搞的
or that Chinese hack I hired to fix the website.
不是  我是在买格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡
No, I'm trying to get tickets
美国知名女歌手  出生于古巴
是她将拉丁音乐打进美国市场
今晚演唱会的门票
for tonight's Gloria Estefan concert.
这有点太巧了吧
That's a little on the nose.
妈  又变成这样啦
Mom, it happened again!
杰  你坐在这仔细盯着
Jay, sit down here and pay attention.
等轮到你的时候必须迅速出手
Ugh! You have to move fast when it's your turn,
不然他们就转到下一个人了
or they'll move to the next person.
乔  这就是为什么我们要等到你6岁
Joe, this is exactly why we're not giving you a knife
才让你玩刀
until you turn 6 years old.
我真怀念那些
I missed the days
人们得实际去排队的日子
when people stood in actual lines.
如果你不愿意在下雨天站着苦等
If you weren't willing to stand in the rain,
你就没资格去看加里·帕克特与联盟峡
you didn't get to see Gary Puckett & the Union Gap.
六十年代的流行摇滚乐队
我靠
Ow! Damn it!
什么  我才溜号一秒
What? It was one second!
好了  给我吧
Okay, give it back to me.
不用了  我买完了
No need. I got 'em.
真的吗  你付完款了吗
Oh, really? And you paid?
付了  用浏览器
Yeah, you got your browser
填一下信用卡信息
filling out your credit card info.
其实这样不太安全
It's not super secure,
不过不论卡被谁偷了
but, whoever steals them
他可能都没你花得多
will probably spend less than you.
多波美丽的早上啊
Oh, what a B-U-tiful morning.
开个玩笑  因为我被波士顿大学录取了
I joke because I've been accepted to B.U.
曼尼  我真为你骄傲
Oh, Manny, I'm so proud of you!
目前六所学校都录取我了
I'm six for six.
这么多追求者  真不知道该选谁
So many suitors -- not sure which to choose from.
我觉得自己就像
I feel like Lady Mary
上一季《唐顿庄园》里的大小姐玛丽
in the last season of "Downton Abbey."
我要是你就不选以美式足球闻名的学校
I'd avoid the big football schools.
今晚我们要去庆祝一下
And tonight we're going to celebrate.
我们要去看演唱会
We're going to a concert.
我在网上买好票了
I got the tickets online.
网上是比去会场买方便些吧
Easier than buying them at the venue, I guess.
会场在哪啊  随口一问
What is the venue, uh, by the way?
不能去会场门口买的
You can't buy them at the door.
是私人演唱会
It's a private concert.
只有粉丝俱乐部的人才能买票
It's just for the fan club.
我还记得我们第一次去
I remember our first
格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡的演唱会
Gloria Estefan concert.
那时你还那么小
You were so little,
坐在我的肩膀上  举着打火机
sitting on my shoulders, holding the lighter.
我要走了
I'm gonna leave.
是啊  一转眼就要离我而去了
Yes, before I know it.
不  是现在要出门
No, right now.
我需要买件新衣服今晚穿
I obviously need something to wear tonight.
好  我和你一起去
Oh, okay. I'll go with you.
多好的主意  去吧  好好玩一天
What a great idea. Go! Make a day of it.
不行  等一下
No, wait, wait, wait --
我不能穿在家穿的高跟鞋去商场
I can't go to the mall wearing my house heels.
那不正是买新鞋的好理由吗
What a good excuse to buy a nice pair of new ones.
这就是为什么我这么爱你
That's why I love you.
什么时候都别忘了这点
Always remember that.
太感谢您了  派太太
Thank you so much, Mrs. Pasternak.
我想您肯定很好奇我为什么向您要骨灰吧
I'm sure you're wondering why I want these ashes.
并没有
Not really,
但你得把骨灰瓮还给我
but I'm gonna need the urn back.
我要把它改造成台灯
I'm gonna turn it into a lamp.
-你好啊  米奇尔  -天啊
- Hello, Mitchell. - Oh, God!
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
你看起来"灰"头土脸的
You're looking a little ashen.
我没事  我不小心把猪莉莉的骨灰弄撒了
I'm fine. I-I-I accidentally spilled pig Lily's ashes,
我本来打算
and I-I thought that I would --
你打算用派先生的骨灰偷梁换柱
You would just replace them with Morris Pasternak's?
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
他的毕业戒指就在你脚边
His class ring is by your foot.
那只宠物猪曾是我最好的朋友
Oh, yeah. ‭That pig was my best friend.
她妈不是被你吃掉的吗
Didn't you eat her mother?
你根本毫不尊重那些对我重要的事物
You know, you have no respect for anything that's important to me.
我的整个成长过程对你而言就是个大笑话
My whole upbringing is just a big joke to you.
大爸  我刚刚在想今晚的猪月葬礼
Dad, I was thinking about the Pig Moon funeral tonight
还有猪莉莉对你有多重要
and how important Lily was to you.
你太贴心了
Aww, that is so sweet.
你绝对继承了她的同情心
You definitely inherited her compassion.
你记得我画的那幅猪莉莉的手指画吗
Remember that finger painting that I made of her,
你说够格在博物馆展出的那幅
the one that you said that was museum quality?
能把画和骨灰一起下葬吗
Can we bury it with her?
我清楚记得画在哪
I know exactly where it is.
我清楚记得画本来在哪
I know exactly where it was.
是我母校给卢克发来的电邮
It's an e-mail for Luke from my alma mater.
-快把他叫来  -先别
- Let's get him! - ‭Oh, no, no!
别叫  万一是坏消息呢
No, what if it's more bad news?
或许你该先读一下
Maybe you should read it first.
克莱尔  我和你一样等不及想知道
Claire, I am as anxious as you are
他会不会和他爸一样成为斗牛犬的一员
to find out if he's gonna be a Bulldog like his old man,
但我们不能侵犯他对我们的信任
but we can't violate his trust.
虽然我们可以重新标记为未读来湮灭证据
Sure, we could mark it as unread to cover our tracks,
但我们心知肚明...
but we'd know --
他没被录取
He didn't get in.
什么  他比别人都强
What?! He's a legacy!
斗牛犬对他垂涎三尺
Bulldog drool courses through his jowls!
我知道  而且这是他第七次被拒了
I know, and it's his seventh rejection.
他会特别失望的
He's gonna be so disappointed.
也会难堪  我们今晚在杰家聚餐
And embarrassed. We have that dinner at Jay's tonight.
我打赌曼尼被所有学校录取了
I bet Manny got in everywhere.
老天
Oh, God.
到此为止了吗
Is this it?
卢克上不成大学了吗
I mean, is Luke not going to college?
还没完
It's not over.
删除
Delete.
你要做什么
What are you doing?
我要开车去那里  告诉他们这是错误的决定
I'm driving up there to tell them they made a mistake.
收一个像卢克这样的学生是他们走运
They'd be lucky to have a kid like Luke.
应该坏不到哪里去
Well, I guess it -- it can't hurt.
他们又不能"超级"拒收
I mean, it's not like they can super reject him.
虽然密歇根大学的确用了这词
Although, Michigan did use that exact term.
这里是96.3潮流台  我们是迪亚哥与傻驴
You're on Caliente 96.3 with Diego and The Donkey.
你好  太棒了
Hello! Yes!
我打来是想获得格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡的票
I'm calling about the Gloria Estefan tickets.
只要你能接上下面的歌词  票就归你了
And they're all yours if you can complete this lyric --
扭转"啥啥"
"Turn the blank around."
她在90年代最火的歌之一
One of her biggest hits from the '90s.
我们今早一直在放
We've been playing it all morning.
-"扭转车..."  -不对  还有两次机会
- "Turn the car around." - Nope. Two more guesses.
"扭转船"
"Turn the boat around."
再试一次
Try again.
"扭转经济"
"Turn the economy around"!
你个蠢驴
You're an ass.
靠
Damn it!
我被密歇根大学"超级录取"了
I just got super accepted to Michigan.
他是迪尔加多家族第二个上大学的人
He's the second Delgado to go to college.
我表哥去了哥伦比亚最好的医学院
My cousin went to the best medical school in Colombia.
那里可不是什么尸体都收的
They would not just accept any cadaver.
行了  妈  我们走
Okay, Mom, let's go.
好  不过先等下
Oh, yeah, but wait.
还记得你脑袋这么小的时候吗
You remember when your head was this tiny?
行了  妈  我已经挑好帽子了
Okay. Mom, Mom, I think I'm set for hats.
女人想大哭时  我看得出来
I know when a female's about to burst into tears.
我看过够多次了
I've seen it enough times.
我得让我妈远离
I had to keep my mom away
任何会让她想到我要离开的东西
from anything that reminded her I was moving away
也让我自己远离厨房用品店
and keep myself away from Williams Sonoma.
我可能会耗掉整个下午在里面
I could lose an afternoon.
宠物店  又萌又有趣
A pet store. These are fun.
我觉得它想妈妈了
I think he misses his mommy.
我们走到车边时它估计就忘掉妈妈吗
He'll forget about her by the time we get to the car.
再一想  我们去看电影吧
On second thought, let's catch a movie.
电影总能让人忘了烦恼
They always help keep your mind off of things.
噗  我娶了我妈
等等  警官  不要
Wait, Officer -- No!
我的车停在这里是因为我是负责任的人
My car is only here because I was being responsible!
我负责照看我舅乔
I was babysitting my uncle Joe
结果喝得太醉不能开车回家了
and got too drunk to drive home!
这是什么鬼东西
What is this thing?!
挡风玻璃锁
The Barnacle.
没交停车罚单  警察就把它贴你车上
They stick it on your car when you have unpaid parking tickets.
我不能让爸妈看到
I couldn't let my parents see it,
因为我知道他们会小题大做
because I knew they'd just overreact
给我讲一堆要负责的大道理
and lecture me about being irresponsible,
我也不能付罚单移除这东西
and I couldn't pay to remove it
因为我刚刷爆了信用卡
because I just maxed out my credit card
买了副超贵的太阳镜
on these insanely expensive pair of sunglasses.
我也不想
I don't love 'em.
我只要重新画一张莉莉的猪莉莉画
I just had to re-create Lily's painting of Pig Lily,
她就不会知道那件事
and she'd be none the wiser.
天  就像用香肠画画似的
Oh, it's like painting with sausages.
抱歉  小卡  这里没有莉莉画的小猪画
Sorry, Cam, no pig painting by Lily here.
不过有一些涂鸦
I do have some random scribbles
是卢克还小的时候画...
that Luke made when he was...
好像是比我希望的岁数还大些时画的
Huh, that's a little later than I'd hoped.
好  这事绝不能告诉米奇尔
Fine. Not a word of this to Mitchell.
我知道你好奇原因
I'm sure you're curious why.
你又错了
Wrong again.
你是第一个到的
Hi. You're the first one here.
别担心  我们不必闲聊的
Don't worry. We don't have to make conversation.
剪贴簿
Ooh! A scrapbook!
瞧瞧
Aww, look at this.
我们小时候的学校作业都在
All of our old school projects --
我和克莱尔画的画
paintings by me and Claire.
你就是个豆腐心啊
Aww! You're just a big softie, aren't 'cha?
我律师的秘书整的
My lawyer's secretary put that together
为了我在离婚法庭上的形象
for my image at the divorce trial.
还是原来强硬的熊爸
There's the old bear. Grr!
这是我八岁生日时照的
Oh, this is from my 8th birthday.
我让妈给我办了场农场主题的派对
I made Mom throw a party with a whole farm theme.
猜怎么着  我需要这张照片
You know what? I need this.
小卡觉得我看不起他的农场生活
Cam thinks I look down on his farm life.
-这能证明给他看...  -停停停
- This'll prove to him that... - Bup, bup, bup.
要照片得付出代价
This comes with a price.
你能给我弄到格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡的票吧
You can get me Gloria Estefan tickets, right?
爸  这话有点冒犯人
Dad, that is offensive.
不是所有同性恋都跟她有交情
Not every gay person is connected to Gloria Estefan.
但你有  对吧
But you are, right?
情况很复杂
It's complicated.
小卡曾和格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡的
Cam briefly dated a member
迈阿密之音乐队的一员约过会
of Gloria Estefan's band, The Miami Sound Machine.
他不常提起
He doesn't talk about it much.
也就有人提到她或迈阿密就说吧
Just whenever someone mentions her or Miami.
还有湿度
Or humidity.
就这样
Well...
一手给票  一手给照片
when I get the tickets, you get the picture.
小气
Mean!
你愿不愿意请小卡动用他的关系
Um, how would you feel about asking Cam to use his connections
弄到两张今晚看格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡的票
to get two Gloria Estefan tickets for tonight
然后偷偷给我
and then secretly giving them to me?
我愿意做
I'll do it,
但你要先帮我办车的事
but I need you to help me with my car first.
我可以找我爸妈  但...
I'd ask my parents, but --
他们不会理解  这不是你的错
They wouldn't understand. It's not your fault.
行  我们快去
Yeah. Okay. Let's go.
你确定这是最好的办法吗
Are we sure this is the best way to do this?
我们只需要确保我爸妈不会看到它
All we have to do is make sure that my parents don't see it
我们往前开点就行了
by moving it down the street.
-懂吗  抓好  -我就是你的眼
- Okay? Hold on. - I'm your eyes.
沿着路边
Hug the curb.
海莉...  好吧  直着开
Haley, just -- all right. Straighten out.
开启危险警告灯
T-Turn on your hazards.
-那是雨刷  -你踩到我腿了  挪开
- That's the windshield wiper! - You're on my leg! Move!
天啊  有棵树...
Oh, God! There's a tree.
好吧
All right.
我们先喘口气  等一下
Let's just breathe, let's take a moment...
你能从我腿上挪开吗
Can you just get off my leg, please?
对不...  我没有...
I'm not -- I'm s-- I'm not --
-我们在往后吗  -你挂了倒车档
- Are we going backwards? - You put us in reverse.
踩刹车
Okay, hit the brake.
那是油门
That is the gas!
你驾照是怎么考的啊
How do you have a license?!
我动不了  你压到我腿了
I can't move! You're on my leg!
好了  第一次尝试还不错
Okay. Good first try.
不敢相信你不来杯斗牛犬冰沙
Can't believe you didn't treat yourself to a Bulldog Blast.
那不就是糖  冰
Isn't that basically just sugar, ice,
还有用来涂蓝人乐队的蓝油漆吗
and the stuff they you use to cover the Blue Man Group?
我们来见招生办主任
We're here to see the Dean of Admissions.
我们来过电话  邓菲家
We called. We're the Dunphys.
我会告诉欣登主任你们到了
Ah. I'll tell Dean Hinden you're here.
欣登吗
Um, eh -- Hinden?
是的  鲁道夫·欣登主任
Yes. Dean Rudolf Hinden.
我有不好的感觉
I have a bad feeling.
亲爱的  你的确刚喝了那像防冻剂的饮料
Well, honey, you did just have two of those antifreezes.
不是啦
No.
鲁迪·欣登  我们曾是同学
Rudy Hinden -- We were classmates.
超烦人  总是很亢奋
Super annoying -- always "on."
我们都是拉拉队的  一起玩蹦床
We cheered together, we -- we tumbled together,
一起四处玩
we rolled around together,
但我们关系从不亲密
but we were never close.
我说斗牛  你说犬
When I say "Bull," you say "Dog"!
-斗牛  -犬
- Bull! - ‭Dog!
你好  鲁迪
‭Hey, Rudy!
这位是我太太克莱尔
This is my wife Claire.
-你好  -很荣幸
- Hi. - ‭Pleasure.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
快请进吧
Well, please come on in.
-蹦床不错啊  -谢谢
- Oh! Great trampoline. - ‭Thanks.
我习惯每天跳至少20分钟
I like to bounce at least 20 minutes a day.
-我的好点子都是在蹦跳中产生的  -好吧
- It's where I get my best ideas. - ‭Okay.
真是个怪人啊
How quirky.
对了  菲尔
Oh, hey, Phil,
当年的高年级比赛在哪里举行
where were Nationals senior year?
克利夫兰  俄"嗨"俄州
Cleveland, Oh-- Hi-o!
你能想象忍受这种怪胎
Can you imagine putting up with this
-很多年的心情吗  -的确很难
- for years on end? - It's hard.
这样吧  我去跳一会找灵感
Tell you what, I'll give it some bounce time
回头给你答复
and hit you back with an answer.
你好像挺忙的
Listen, you seem busy.
那我就直说了
I'll get straight to it.
我们儿子卢克申请了这里  但没被录取
Our son Luke applied and didn't get in,
我觉得你可以再考虑一下
and I think it's worth reconsidering.
他是个好孩子  只是大器晚成
He's a great kid. He's just a late bloomer.
好的  我应该能帮你儿子搞定这事
Okay. I think we can make something happen for your boy.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  比他更糟糕的学生我们也录取过了
Yeah, we've let in way worse applicants than him.
-鲁迪  -什...
- Rudy! - Wha--
-太谢谢了  你最木奉棒了  -是啊
- Thank you! You're the B-E-S-T best! - ‭Yeah.
不客气
No problemo.
我只要...
I'll just, uh...
对了
Hey.
既然你都来了
While you're here,
有件事我一直想问你
I've always wanted to ask you something.
你还记得以前你常表演的那个魔术吗
You remember that magic trick you used to do
就是你蒙着眼从紧身服里挣脱出来那个
where you got out of a straitjacket blindfolded?
巴纳姆骗局
Barnum's Humbug.
对  就是那个
Yeah. That one.
你是怎么做到的
How'd you do it?
用魔法  我觉得应该...
Magic. I-I feel like --
不不不  说真的
No, no, no, really --
我已经试图破解这个魔术好几年了
I've been trying to figure it out for years.
很抱歉
Um, I'm sorry.
按照惯例
It's -- It's not customary
魔术师不可以透露自己的手法
for a magician to reveal his secrets.
按照惯例  招生办主任也不应该
It's also not "customary" for a Dean of Admissions
修改申请人的录取状态  所以...
to alter an applicant's status, so...
我去护士那里拿紧身服过来
I'll go get the straitjacket from the nurse.
你会照做的吧
You're gonna do it, right?
我不知道
I don't know.
让我蹦一会想想
Let me bounce on it.
菲尔
Phil.
亲爱的
Sweetheart?
菲尔  亲爱的  这件事情
Phil. Honey, Phil, you can't possibly
你还有什么好挣扎的
be struggling with this decision.
你知道透露魔术手法的魔术师
Do you know what happens to magicians
会有什么下场吗  克莱尔
who reveal their secrets, Claire?
会被唾弃  会被孤立
They're shunned.
现实不已经是这样了吗
Doesn't that happen already?
我掌握的知识
Listen, I possess knowledge
可是由古埃及巫师
passed down from the ancient Egyptian conjurers
传给黑暗时代的变戏法人
to the prestidigitators of the Dark Ages
再传到今天的业余魔术师手上
to the amateur illusionists of today.
我担心的是另一个戏法
I am worried about another trick.
我正努力把我们儿子"变"到
I am trying to make our son disappear
一所勉强合格的四年制大学里
to a barely accredited four-year college.
-他来了  -好了  我拿来了
- There he is. - Okay, here we are.
你快点穿上吧
Why don't you go ahead and put these on.
不不不  就在这里穿
No, no, no. In here.
我想确保我能学会
I want to make sure I get this.
我要看到一切细节
I want to see everything.
好吧
‭Okay.
好  我帮你拿着
Okay, I got it.
我当时还没意识到我叫菲尔做的事有多严重
I didn't quite grasp what I was asking Phil to do,
不过...
but, um...
后来越变越怪了
it got weird.
好了
Okay.
好  你准备好就随时可以开始
All right. Whenever you're ready.
等等  这不会被放到网上吧
Wait, th-this isn't going on the Internet, is it?
不会  我自己看而已
No, it's just for me.
这套逃脱术的诀窍是
The challenge with this escape
按正确顺序解开锁链
is, uh, releasing the shackles in the correct order
再慢慢从中挣脱出来
baring yourself gradually.
-再欢乐一点  要说台词  -什么
- Okay, more upbeat. Do the patter. - What?
我想听以前那套台词
I want to hear the old patter.
蒙住他的眼睛
Blindfold him.
-拿着  -是  长官
- Take it. - ‭Yes...sir.
菲尔
Phil.
亲爱的  你不必这么做
Honey, you don't have to do this.
大不了卢克可以去参军
Luke can join the army.
没关系
It's okay.
肉体虽被困住  但我心是自由的
I may be locked up, but my mind is free.
好了
Okay.
想象你正在一个博物馆里
Imagine yourself in a museum
里面摆满了来自世界各地的奇异之物
filled with the world's oddities.
不不不  慢一点说
No, no, no, no. Slow down.
享受过程
Enjoy it.
转过去
And turn around
我要看清楚背面
so I can get a good look at the back.
让我看背面
Let me see the back.
屏息以待
Behold the freak
奇事即将发生
for all to see.
帮我拿到门票
Go get my tickets.
我头发是不是很塌
Is my hair a mess?
今天外面好潮湿
It's so humid out.
你想讨论湿度吗
You want to talk about humidity?
我曾经跟迈阿密之音乐队的
I once spent a steamy weekend
一位成员共度了一个很"湿"的周末
with a certain member of the Miami Sound Machine.
太巧了吧
‭That's crazy!
-你知道他们今晚就在城里吗  -什么
- Do you know that they're in town tonight? - What?
你能帮我弄两张票吗
Can you get me two tickets?
天啊
Oh, my God.
这双玉手
These hands --
如此精致小巧  像孩子的手一样
they're so small and delicate like a child.
我知道
I know.
这块手表本来是芭比娃娃戴的
This watch came from an American Girl doll.
-你到底能不能帮我搞到票  -可以
- Are you gonna hook me up or what? - ‭Yes, yes.
但你得先用那双小手
Just as soon as you and your tiny little hands
帮我重画一幅画
re-create a painting for me.
这边请
This way.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我追求的是阴暗神秘高冷风
I was going for dark and mysterious,
但恐怕还是回到了
but I'm afraid I circled right back
可爱亲切暖男风
to cute and approachable.
她真幸运
Oh, she's so lucky.
他永远都会是她的小宝贝
He's always gonna be her little boy.
妈  你把自己的心情投射到假人身上了
Mom, you're projecting on these mannequins.
说不定他是个侏儒
For all we know, he's a little person,
而这位是他的老婆  有足够成熟的心
and that's his wife who's evolved enough
能看到他内心有多么高大
to see how big he is on the inside.
曼尼  我知道你这一整天
Manny, I know what you've been
都在打什么主意
trying to do the whole day.
我不会因为你要去上大学
I am not about to have a breakdown
就精神崩溃
because you're going to college.
你昨晚帮我梳头的时候  我其实没睡着
I was awake last night when you were brushing my hair.
好吧  我的确是会很难受
Okay, yes, it's going to be hard
因为你要去很远的地方
because you're gonna be far away,
我就不能常常见到你了
so I'm not gonna get to see you all the time.
但我们还是会打电话啊
But we'll still talk on the phone.
一开始会
Yeah, at the beginning,
但接着你就会忙学业
but then you're gonna get busy,
我也有自己的事要忙
and then I am going to get busy.
你会忙到接不了我的电话吗
Too busy to take my calls?
我已经想通了
I have made peace with it.
你的童年时期已经结束了
Your childhood days are over.
吉列尔莫  回来
Guillermo, come back here!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
不要从你母亲身边跑走
Don't run away from your mother.
很快生活就会迫使你们分别
Life is going to tear you apart soon enough.
我想去坐旋转木马
I want to go on the merry-go-round.
你的人生就是走马灯
Oh, you're on it.
你和她只剩下十年的相处时间了
You've got 10 years left with that woman.
珍惜这段时间  珍惜她
Cherish them. Cherish her.
谢谢
Thanks?
似乎我才是因为要上大学而慌张的那个人
I think maybe I'm freaking out about going to school.
我看到了
I see that.
但我们会没事的
But we're gonna be okay.
我们的分离只会让每个夜晚像今晚一样精彩
Being apart is just gonna make nights like tonight,
去看演唱会  或者有更特别的安排
going to a concert, even more special.
-不  -吉列尔莫
- No! ‭- Guillermo!
我不想去
I don't want to!
这死小孩只是没家教罢了
Okay, now it's just bad parenting.
这活儿太好了
This is excellent work.
-太棒了  -真的吗
- Excellent work. - ‭Really?
好不习惯听到这话啊
I'm not used to hearing that.
终于懂别人做事为何会努力了
I get why people try now.
那是我的画吗
Is that my painting?
为什么在这里
Why is it here?
因为之前被借走了
Um, oh, well, because it was on loan
你祖父祖母借去摆了
to your grandma and grandpa
他们也这么借真艺术品
just like they do with real art.
比这家里大多数的艺术品强多了
Better than most of the stuff in this house.
给我去弄格洛丽亚·埃斯特巴的票
Now get me those Gloria Esteban tickets.
是埃斯特凡
It's Estefan.
我就是这么说的啊  我可是脑残粉
That's what I said. I'm a huge fan.
好吧
Okay.
卡洛斯  卡洛斯
Carlos, Carlos.
你好  卡洛斯
Hey -- hey, Carlos.
我是卡梅隆·塔克
Um, this, uh, Cameron Tucker.
我也不确定你还记不记得我
I don't know if you remember me or not.
你...  你记得啊
Oh, you -- you do.
好久不见啊
Okay, hi.
我能不能麻烦你帮我弄几张
Yeah, wondering if I could get a couple tickets
今晚演出的票
for the show tonight.
格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡
Gloria Estefan.
因为你是迈阿密之音乐队的成员啊  傻子
Because you're in the Miami Sound Machine, silly.
什么
What?
我遇到卡洛斯的那晚  酒吧很吵
It was loud in the bar the night I met Carlos,
结果发现他并不是
and it turns out he is not a member
那个传奇乐队  迈阿密之音的成员
of the legendary band, the Miami Sound Machine.
他有一个狗狗美容车的生意
He owns a mobile dog grooming business
名叫"迈阿狗之净"
called Miami's Hound Machine.
现在一看  我当时不该因他拥有
In retrospect, I didn't need to be as alarmed
这么多绳索与颈圈而起戒心
with his collection of leashes and collars.
大伙们聚过来
Okay, everybody, gather round.
卢克还有一家大学的回复没看
Luke has one more college to hear from,
我感觉这家挺有戏呢
and I got a good feeling about this one.
对啊
Yeah.
妈  我们能别在这里看吗
Mom, can we not do this here?
没事啦  要有点信心
Oh, come on, have a little faith.
礼炮已备好  开始录制
Okay, cannon's ready. And record.
录  好了
Record, got it.
随时开始  小家伙
Any time, buddy.
好啦各位
All right, everyone,
准备好安慰我天生我材必有用
get ready to tell me how I'm my own kind of smart
老天爷自有安排
and how everyone takes their own path.
天生我材必有用  老天...
You're a different kind of smart, and everyone...
必有用  老天爷自有安排
Kind of smart. Everybody takes their own path.
我被录取啦
I got in?
什么  他进啦
What?! He got in!
他进啦
He got in!
你进啦  这玩意什么毛病
You got in! ‭What is wrong with this thing?
等等  这不科学啊
Wait, this doesn't make any sense.
我都被更差的学校拒绝过了
I got rejected by worse schools than this.
他们为什么会要收我啊
Why would they want me?
人家为什么会不要你
Why wouldn't they want you?
宝贝  不只是学术成绩重要啊
Honey, it's not all about grades.
你还参加了很多...
I mean, you were involved in -- in...
你们跟学校谈过了吗
Did you talk to them?
你说什么  没听清
I'm sorry, what?
舌头伸出来给我看
Show me your tongue.
我伸舌头又能证明什么呢
I don't know what that would prove.
这感觉是个尴尬的家庭时刻
This kind of seems like an embarrassing family moment.
已经在录了
I know, I'm on it.
蓝色
‭Blue!
去过那学校的人
You can't go to that campus
肯定都尝过他们的斗牛犬冰沙
without getting a Bulldog Blast.
我们是去告诉他们  不录取你是错误
We went up there to tell them they made a mistake.
他们并没有犯错误
They didn't make a mistake,
其他不要我的学校也没有做错
and neither did the other schools.
我不会去上的
I'm not going.
宝贝  这是你最后的机会了
Honey, it's your last chance.
那我就明年再去上
Then I'll wait until next year.
-要去  就得是正大光明进去  -这话我服
- If I go, I want to deserve it. - I can respect that.
没人让你提供意见  谢谢
Nobody asked for your opinion, thank you.
你必须得去上
You're going.
你完全不知道你爸爸费了多大功夫
You have no idea what your father went through
才为你弄到这机会
to get you this opportunity.
以你无法想象到的方式牺牲自己人格
He debased himself in ways you can't imagine.
你不是说没多严重吗
You said it wasn't that bad.
你在看什么
What are you watching?
我们的邻居发给我个视频
Our neighbor sent me a video.
是海莉跟米奇尔
It's of Haley and Mitchell.
不是  那是...  不需要放出...
Oh. No, that's -- okay, we don't need to...
太久了吧
It's taking forever.
我已经用全身力气推了
I'm pushing as hard as I can.
你的挡风玻璃被人安上那东西了吗
You have one of those things on your windshield?
你收到了多少张停车罚单啊
How many parking tickets do you have?
我觉得现在焦点不应该在我啊
I think we're focused on the wrong thing here.
卢克不去上大学了呢
Luke's not going to college.
你的手指为什么是粉色的
Why is your finger pink?
这不是我画的
This isn't mine.
我就觉得作图视角怪怪的
I knew the perspective was off.
是小卡的错
It's Cam's fault.
他让我看着照片做出来的
He made me copy it from a photo.
是这样的  我不小心毁了原件
You know what? I accidentally destroyed the original,
我心里又过意不去
and I couldn't live without it.
米奇尔·普里契特  我代表"育儿杂志"提问
Mitchell Pritchett, Parenting Magazine.
伪造孩子的画就有比用派太太亡夫骨灰
How is forging a child's painting any less egregious
来替换猪的骨灰强到哪里去吗
than replacing a pig's ashes with Mrs. Pasternak's dead husband?
没有
It's not.
我就是个伪君子  我的一生充满谎言
I'm a hypocrite. My whole life is a lie.
卡洛斯并不是迈阿密之音的团员
Carlos isn't really in the Miami Sound Machine.
他只是个...  普通的狗狗美容师
He's just a -- a basic dog groomer.
把钱省下来吧  我不能帮你弄到票
Save your money. I couldn't get you your tickets.
你花钱去买票
You're spending money on tickets
而不是花钱去付掉罚票[单]吗...
when you should be spending money on ticket --
你懂我的意思
you know what I mean.
演唱会的票是帮米奇尔弄的
The concert tickets were for Mitchell.
-所以你没帮我搞来门票吗  -没有
- So you didn't get my tickets? - ‭No.
-你没帮我买到票啊  -那网站像神经病
- So you didn't get my tickets. - The website was insane.
没有猫鼬般的反应速度根本抢不到
You'd need the reflexes of a mongoose.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
看看大家  谁都在说谎
Well, look around! Everybody's lying.
伪造画作  盲眼开车
Forging paintings, driving blind,
偷换骨灰
swapping ashes.
我不想毁了你的猪月嘛
I didn't want to ruin the Pig Moon.
没有什么猪月好吗
There is no Pig Moon.
你是觉得我密苏里老家有多落后啊
How backwards do you think Grasshopper, Missouri is?
大家听我说  我能解决
Guys, guys. I've got this.
各位
Guys.
我打给塔格法官了
I talked to Judge Tager.
他同意撤销你的罚单
He'll make your parking tickets disappear
代价是给他来俩上好古巴雪茄
in return for a couple of Cubans.
你拿了三根
You took three.
另一根是给俱乐部的保安的
The other one is for the security guard at the club.
他今晚在埃斯特凡的演唱会兼职保安
He moonlights where Estefan's playing tonight.
你们到时候入口见
He'll meet you by the stage door.
谢谢你帮杰圆了谎
Thank you for fixing Jay's lies.
我们都对说出实话感到棘手
We all struggle with the truth.
就像上周四我帮你把杰拖在俱乐部
like last Thursday when I stalled Jay at the club
好让你有时间把乔弄出狗门
so you could get Joe out of the doggy door.
她不小心把我俩锁门外了  而瓦斯炉又没关
She locked us out, and the stove was on.
-至于你们两个  -你有认识人能帮忙吗
- And you two. - You know a guy at a club that can help us?
没有  你们多谈谈就行了
No. Just talk more.
你们9成的问题
90% of your problems would be solved
都只需要多谈谈就能解决
if you just discussed things.
家里的范德考夫沙发是山寨货
The Vanderkoff is a knock-off.
我不小心把山寨货烫出了个洞
I burnt a hole in the knock-off,
所以买了个新的真品替换
and I had replaced it with a real one.
好了  所有问题都解决了
Okay, everything's settled here.
我觉得牛排好了  我们去吃饭吧
I think the steaks are ready. Let's go eat.
看来我们的儿子
Well, I guess our son
今年是不会去上大学了
isn't going to college this year.
是啊  而我们本来应该很担心他
I know, and I know we're supposed to be worried about him.
但你看到他刚才做的了吗
But do you see what he just did,
他怎么帮大家解决问题
how he solved everybody's problems like that?
还挺厉害的吧
It's pretty incredible, right?
他是个邓菲家的好男儿啊  克莱尔
That's a Dunphy man, Claire --
足智多谋  临危不乱
resourceful, cool,
以及恰到好处的随机应变力
and just the right amount of savoir faire.
我...  我们厨房见
I'll, uh -- I'll see you in the kitchen.
所以这是真的范德考夫沙发啊
So this is a real Vanderkoff.
对啊  从这秘密中解放出来太爽了
Yeah, yeah. Feels good to finally be free of that secret.
对啊  把事情都摊开来说感觉太好了
Yeah, it's just... great to have everything out in the open.
是啊
Yeah.
那边你买来送我的名贵油画
That expensive painting you bought me over there,
我移动他是为了挡墙上我弄出来的洞
I moved it to cover up a hope I made in the wall.
我是在人家二手拍卖的时候花2毛5买的
I only paid 25 cents for that painting at a garage sale.
剩下的钱我拿去买鞋了
I used the rest of the money on shoes
我有做电流除毛  不然我胡子会长到这
I get electrolysis. My beard grows up to here.
我其实不会跳排舞
I don't really know how to line dance,
所以我教你的时候  那些牛仔都在笑你
and that's why those cowboys laught at you when I taught you.
-那不是拉里  -那不是拉里
- That's not Larry - That's not Larry.